（意大利塞纳莱斯阿尔卑斯滑雪度假村）
目标正在接近
Target approaching.
斯通 情况如何？
Stone, how we doing?
差不多了 正在获取加密密钥
Almost there. Just pulling the encryption key.
在车里待了四小时 她把薯片都吃光了
Four hours in the van, and she's eaten all the crisps.
她跟你一起被困在车上
She's stuck in there with you,
只能借吃消愁
So that's comfort eating.
你又聊猫 让她觉得无趣了？
Been boring her with your cat chat again?
猫咪聊天？事实上，帕克，她喜欢我讲的猫巴里的故事
Cat chat? Actually, Parker, she likes my Barry the Cat stories.
你喜欢听我讲巴里猫的故事 对吧？
You like my Barry the Cat stories, right?
嘿 你不知不觉就想自己当铲屎官了
Before you know it, you're gonna want one of your own.
猫视我为敌 抱歉 贝利
Cats hate me. Sorry, Bailey.
我在编写新的访问代码
Writing a new access code.
谢谢
Grazie.
我看到穆菲尼了
I have eyes on Mulvaney.
情报准确
Intel was good.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
欧洲头号军火通缉犯三年来首度现身
Europe's most wanted arms dealer seen for the first time in three years.
我把姓名和照片添加到宾客名单上
Adding names and faces to the guest list.
-还要多久？-快好了
-How long do you need? -Nearly there.
等等 有状况 我连不上网络
Hang on. Something's changed. I can't connect.
系统离线了
The system's offline.
只能本地访问
Local access only.
我们需要另想办法 让你们混进去
We need a new plan to get you in.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我需要直接连已接通网络的人
I need direct access to someone who's already on the network.
保安主管 他在酒吧
Head of security. He's at the bar.
我可以黑进他的手机 但我得靠近他才行
I could hack his phone, but I'll need to be close to him.
-要多近？-三米
-How close? -Ten feet.
斯通 你不是外勤探员 别下车
Stone, you're not a field agent. Do not get out of the van.
她可以的
She can do this.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
穆菲尼现在进来了
Mulvaney's entering now.
这位军火商正在行动中 我不想把他跟丢了
Our arms dealer's on the move right now, and I do not wanna lose him.
别无他法 我们必须逮住穆菲尼
There's no other way. We have to get Mulvaney.
你需要什么 告诉我
Tell me what you need.
当我离保安队长不到十英尺的时候，就打他的电话
When I'm within ten feet of the head of security, call his phone.
好 明白
Okay, got it.
嘿 斯通
Hey. Hey, Stone.
你能搞定
You got this.
谢了 贝利
Thanks, Bailey.
我没法继续跟踪他们了
I can't tail them any further.
斯通，听我说 服务员在你右边
Stone, listen to me. Waiter to your right.
拿一杯香槟
Grab a glass of champagne.
-谢谢 -很好 现在把香槟喝了
-Thank you. -Good. Now, drink it.
喝酒壮胆
Liquid courage.
他朝21点赌桌走过去了
He's headed towards the blackjack table.
你会玩吗？
Do you know how to play?
我以前是国际象棋队的
I was on the chess team.
我的天
Oh my God.
-下注吧 -欢迎
-Just place a bet. -Welcome.
-输了也没关系
Doesn't matter if you lose.
要换吗 先生？没问题 100？
Change set, seven. One hundred.
75、100 换了100 先生
-One hundred, change seven.
好 我可以访问了
Okay, I have access.
先生 100块的零钱 好 各位都准备好了吗？
One hundred, sir, in change. Okay. Everybody ready?
他看起来很可疑
He's looking suspicious.
下注吧
Place your bets.
他朝你那边走过去了
He's headed towards you.
斯通 走开
Stone, walk away.
走开…
-Walk away. Walk away--
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我之前没玩过
I've never played before.
（学玩21点 新手指南）
（"Learning to Play Blackjack: A Beginner's Guide)
-16点 -不好意思
-Sixteen. -I'm sorry.
把两张8分成两墩牌
You split your eights.
把两张8分成两墩牌 18点
Splitting your eights. Eighteen.
18点
Eighteen.
庄家有17点
Dealer has 17.
-你赢了-你赢了
-Ah, you win. -You win it.
或许我应该见好就收
Maybe I should quit while I'm ahead.
谢谢
-Thank you.
干得漂亮 斯通
Nice job, Stone.
第一次外勤任务表现不错
Not bad for your first time out of the van.
刚才让我紧张得折寿了两年
I think I just lost two years off my life.
-搞定了吗？-是的 我连上网了
-Did it work? -Yeah, I'm in.
穆菲尼到底去哪里了？
Where the hell's Mulvaney?
好 找到他了 穿过厨房 下楼
Okay. Got him. Through the kitchen, down the stairs.
有两个大块头把门
Two heavies working the door.
我们马上过去
On our way.
把你们加入到人脸识别系统
Inserting you into facial recognition.
你好 美女
Hello, beautiful.
我可以坐这里吗？
May I take this seat?
去别处坐吧
Take it anywhere you like.
好吧
Okay.
晚点再聊？
Maybe later?
好 你俩都搞定了
Okay, you're all set.
真不知道是什么让穆菲尼重现江湖 我有点担心
I'm almost afraid to see what drew Mulvaney out of his hole.
两位兄弟
-Lads. -Buona sera.
好
Okay.
现在为下一场赌局下注
We're now taking bets for the next game,
两分钟后开始
which will begin in two minutes.
你说穆菲尼好赌 果真如此
You were right about Mulvaney's gambling habit.
他什么都赌
He never met a bet he didn't place.
玩家必须准确预测杀戮的顺序
You must predict the exact order of kills.
收到 DK6 我们已报告有敌人…
Copy, Delta Kilo Six. We have reported hostiles…
那些是军事行动
Those are military operations.
他们赌的是死亡人数
They're wagering on body count.
赌四人当场毙命
With a bet of four instant kills,
这一局的赢家是46号玩家
this is a win for player number 46.
拿人命当赌注
Betting on blood.
小杨 让我看看
Yang, show me.
在你右边一点
Just a bit to your right.
老天
Holy shit.
那是美国海豹突击队的实时画面
That's US Navy Seals in real-time.
他们破解了军事级加密系统
And they've cracked military-grade encryption.
谁有那种能耐？
Who would have that capability?
别聊技术了
Enough tech talk.
目标是穆菲尼
Target is Mulvaney.
好了 杨医生
Okay, Dr. Yang.
接下来看你大显身手
You have the floor.
是时候让穆菲尼心脏病发作了
Time to give Mulvaney his heart attack.
我会发动救护车
I'll fire up the ambulance.
穆菲尼要离开了
Mulvaney's exiting.
该死
Shit.
我来对付这家伙
I'll handle this guy.
你去抓穆菲尼
You take Mulvaney.
斯通
Stone.
穆菲尼在你右侧
Mulvaney's on your right.
另一个员工通道
Another service corridor.
做好准备 我这就切断电源
Stand by to go dark.
该死
Shit.
我抓到穆菲尼了
I've got Mulvaney.
贝利 马上带我们离开这里
Bailey, get us out of here. Fast.
好戏开场！
Showtime!
好吧 好 好吧
All right. Okay. All right.
是军情六处吧？
MI6, right?
你们办事也太张扬了
You guys really need to work on your subtlety.
你们坏了我的好事
You ruined my party.
我真该听从自己的直觉
I should've listened to the voices in my head.
“英国人来了”“英国人来了”
"The British are coming. The British are coming."
通讯系统遭到入侵
Comms compromised.
-不会吧 -好 另谋他法
-No shit. -Okay, okay. New plan.
备选撤退路线 我们要切断通讯
Exfil route Bravo. We have to go dark.
收到 山下见
Copy that. See you down there.
走吧
Come on.
斯通 走吧
Stone! Let's go.
嘿！
Hey!
我又不会逃跑
I'm not going anywhere.
这事儿还没完
We're not done yet.
有很多穆菲尼的手下的人 来了
More of Mulvaney's men.
他们正朝缆车站方向过去
They're heading to the cable car station.
帕克有危险
Parker's a sitting duck.
我们得马上下去
We need to get down there now.
-斯通！-快走 别管我 我没事
-Stone! -Go without me. I'll be fine.
待着别动 我们马上回来
Stay put. We'll be back.
杰克 我是红心九 请提供紧急预测
Jack, this is Nine of Hearts. Urgent forecast required.
九号 已获取你的位置和整体概况
Nine, we have your position and the full overview.
现在进行预测
Projecting forward now.
军情六处小组无法及时下山
The MI6 team won't get down the mountain in time.
据谍心预测 除非特许局干预
and Mulvaney will get away unless the Charter intervenes.
帕克有93%的几率会死 穆菲尼会逃脱
The Heart gives a 93 percent chance that Parker will die
我需要一副降落伞
I'm gonna need a parachute.
好
Okay.
右侧栏杆外 50米处
Fifty meters away, over the handrail to your right.
别暴露身份
And don't blow your cover.
我马上行动
On it.
喂！
Oi!
谍心预测成功率仅有32%
The Heart has a chance of success at just 32 percent.
你在帮倒忙 杰克
Not helping, Jack.
斯通 前方有落差很大的悬崖
Um… Stone, big drop coming up.
落差很大的悬崖
Big drop.
-多大？-超级大
-How big? -The mother of big.
大得惊人
Really, really big.
这下成功率大增
And we're in the game.
听着 我有钱
Look, I've got money.
多到数不胜数
More than you can imagine.
不够多
It wouldn't be enough.
还需八分钟
Eight minutes out.
没法及时赶到
We're not gonna make it.
斯通 穆菲尼的保安队抵达缆车站了
Stone, Mulvaney's security are arriving at the cable car station.
走左侧的路线 你得加快速度
Take the route to your left. You need to pick up the pace.
地势太平 海拔不够高
The terrain's too flat, and you're losing altitude.
如果抄近路到滑雪道
If you cut across to the piste,
可以弄到一辆雪地摩托
you can pick up a snow bike.
电缆 电缆！小心缆线！
Cables! Cables! Cables! Ca--
成功率直线下降
Chance of success just plummeted.
那是因为你缺乏想象力
Only 'cause you've got no imagination.
漂亮
Oh, nice. Nice.
开什么玩笑！
Oh, you're joking!
快点！
Come on!
没有我们 他也能应敌 对吧？
He can hold them off without us, right?
坐稳了！
Hold on!
下个弯道就可以赶超那些雪地摩托
You can get ahead of the bikes at the next corner.
嘿 你没事吧？
Hey. Are you okay?
又见面了
We meet again.
一定是命中注定
Must be destiny.
一定是
Must be.
喂
Hey!
喂！
斯通 小心你右侧的贝利和小杨
Stone, watch Bailey and Yang to your right.
特许局费了很大劲 才把你安插进军情六处
The Charter's worked too hard to embed you in MI6.
我们不能冒险暴露你的身份
We cannot risk your cover.
明白 杰克
Well aware, Jack.
有多少人迎接我啊？
How many in the welcome party?
六个
Six of them.
四个用手枪 一个用霰弹枪 还有一个狙击手
Four pistols, one shotgun, and a sniper
他的狙杀记录令人侧目
with a very impressive record.
闪开！
Get out of the way!
离他们远点 走右侧那条道路
Get away from them. Take the path to your right.
狙击手已向帕克开火
The sniper has opened fire on Parker.
杰克 告诉我怎么做
Jack, tell me what to do.
我把灯灭掉
I got the lights.
小心身后！
Behind you!
成功率上升到85%
Chance of success to 85%.
只有85%？
Only 85%?
说不过去
Hardly seems fair.
你的右侧还有两个
Uh… two more on your right.
瞧瞧看
Look at that.
帕克和目标还活得好好的
Parker and target still very much alive.
太好了
Great.
把尸体藏起来 赶紧离开 免得军情六处的人发现你
Now, hide the bodies and get out before MI6 sees you.
好
Okay.
怎么了？
What's happening?
-小杨 -嘿
-Yang. -Hey.
他们去哪儿了？
Where'd they go?
谁去哪儿了？
Where'd who go?
穆菲尼有一支保安队
Mulvaney had an army of security.
或许被警笛吓跑了？
Got scared off by the sirens maybe?
事不宜迟
No point waiting to find out.
把他带走就行
Let's just grab him and go.
等下！他口吐泡沫
-Whoa, whoa, whoa! He's foaming. -Shit.
这混蛋服了氰化物？
Bastard took cyanide.
这是老派做法
That's old school.
该死
Shit.
老天 他死了
Jesus. He's dead.
抓住一条腿
Grab a leg.
我们得返回山上去接斯通
We have to get back up the mountain for Stone.
好了 天才 现在怎么办？
All right, genius. Now what?
♪ 你无论知道什么都不能说♪
♪ What you don't know cannot ♪
♪ 杀 ♪
♪ Kill ♪
♪ 你无论知道什么都不能说 ♪
♪ What you don't know cannot ♪
♪ 杀 ♪
♪ Kill ♪
♪ 相信我，我想要的就是见到你 ♪
♪ Believe me, all I want is seeing you ♪
♪ 为了自己 因为我已经静默太久 ♪
♪ For myself 'Cause I've been quiet way too long ♪
片名：谍之心
♪ 我一直坚守 ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been ♪
♪ 一，二，三，我实现了我的梦想 ♪
♪ One, two, three, got my classic dreams ♪
♪ 我冰冷的脸，我很自信 ♪
♪ Got a stone-like skin But I might can be ♪
♪  就像坐在前排观看结局的一幕 ♪
♪ Like a front-row seat To the ending scene ♪
♪ 一切都回来了 都回来了♪ ♪
♪ And it's all coming back All running back ♪
♪ 感觉就像来自过去的爆炸 ♪
♪ Feeling like a blast from the past ♪
♪ 衣冠禽兽 手中握着重权 ♪
♪ Beast in the dress It be like a stone in the hands ♪
♪ 所以我会保持低调，保持低调♪
♪ So I'll keep it down, keep it down ♪
♪ 就像秋天一样 拿起枪，拿起枪♪
♪ Just like fall Pick a gun, pick a gun ♪
♪ 为自己而战 做回自己♪
♪ Fight the fight for the one Be the one ♪
♪ 必须吸取教训 没有什么是看起来都是那样的
♪ Gotta learn a lesson Nothing is what it seems ♪
♪ 如果你在读这篇文章，那就意味着我走了，亲爱的♪
♪ If you're reading this It means I'm gone, my dear ♪
♪ 如果可能 我会为你擦干眼泪 ♪
♪ If I only could I would dry your tears ♪
♪ 在你耳边低语 ♪
♪ And whisper in your ear ♪
♪ 但我爱你 ♪
♪ But I love you ♪
♪ 这样我就能保持安静 ♪
♪ This way I keep it quiet ♪
♪ 嘘，嘘，嘘 ♪
♪ Shh, shh, shh ♪
♪ 你无论知道什么都不能说 ♪
♪ What you don't know cannot ♪
♪ 杀 ♪
♪ Kill ♪
♪ 你无论知道什么都不能说 ♪
♪ What you don't know cannot ♪
♪ 杀 ♪
♪ Kill ♪
♪ 相信我，我需要你♪
♪ Believe me, all I want is you ♪
（英国 伦敦）
♪ 为了自己 因为我已经静默太久 ♪
♪ For myself 'Cause I've been quiet way too long ♪
真是一团糟
Genuine dog's breakfast.
意大利方面勃然大怒
The Italians are livid.
国防部和首相府也震怒
As are Defense and Number 10.
我负全责
I take full responsibility.
你的问题就是满嘴只有“我” 帕克
"I." That's your problem, Parker.
穆菲尼死了
Mulvaney's dead.
小杨搞错对象 让另一个人心脏病发作
Yang gave the wrong person a heart attack.
还有斯通
And Stone,
你到底想些什么？居然下车？
what the hell were you thinking getting out of the van?
-只有那样 她才能…-写进报告吧
-That was the only way she could get-- -Put it in the report.
文书工作 好极了
Paperwork. Excellent.
那会让穆菲尼的人明白谁才是老大
That'll show Mulvaney's lads who's boss.
够了
Enough.
穆菲尼已死
Mulvaney's gone.
将他纳为己用的希望也破灭了
And so is any hope of using him as an asset.
不过现在我们有了新的目标
But now we have a new target.
有人闯入最高级别的军事级加密系统
Someone broke through the highest levels of military encryption.
包括我们的加密系统
Including our own.
-你查过那女孩吗？-那女孩？
-Did you look into the girl? -The girl?
查过
Oh, yes.
恐怕我们需要做更多
I'm afraid we'll need more than that.
我们正在想办法追踪她 但目前一无所获
We are trying to trace her, but so far, we have nothing.
-我很乐意去查… -我们有人做这种事
-I'm happy to look-- -We have people for that.
不同的人
Different people.
你们专心写报告吧
You can all concentrate on your admin. Sandra.
珊卓
Cheers, Sandra.
再见 珊卓
Bye, Sandra.
谢了 珊卓
Thanks, Sandra.
爱你 珊卓
Love you, Sandra.
敬斯通
To Stone.
-首次出外勤任务 -嘿！
-First time out of the van. -Hey!
她没搞砸行动 所以…
And she didn't blow the op...
对 是我们自己搞砸的
No, we did that all on our own.
真可惜
Too bad.
自从斯通加入以来 我们一直连战连胜
Been on a good winning streak since Stone joined us.
还以为你或许是我们的福星呢
Thought you might be our lucky charm.
不过你确实赢了21点
But you did win at blackjack.
我戒赌了 也不会再出外勤
And I'm never gambling again or stepping out of the van.
我们离开后 你做了什么？
What'd you do when I left you up there?
在厕所藏身
Hid in the toilets.
-怎么？你们说不要被人发现 -没错
-What? You said to stay out of sight. -True.
好了 放过她吧
All right. Leave her alone.
我们有更重要的事要讨论
We got more important things to discuss.
比如那个女孩
Like, the girl.
说真的 我们已经知道她为谁效力
But let's be honest. We already know who she works for.
-老天 -没错 特许局
-God. -That's right. The Charter.
做好准备
Strap yourselves in.
无所谓了
Whatever.
我刚确认了他们的另一项行动
I just identified another one of their ops.
他们干掉了一个恐怖小组
They took out a terror cell who hijacked
该小组在巴拿马运河劫持了一艘油轮
An oil tanker in the Panama Canal.
是啊 但谁有那种能耐？
Yeah, but who would have that kind of power?
对
Hm.
-我又说这种话了 对吗？
-I'm doing it again, aren't I? -Yeah.
好吧 好 尽管笑我
Okay, fine, mock me.
不过这是真的
But it's true.
只听命于自己的前情报人员
Ex-intelligence operatives answering only to themselves.
不效忠任何国家 没有任何政治倾向
No national allegiances, no political leanings.
摆平政府不允许他们插手的问题
Putting out fires their governments never allowed them to. That's…
特许局就是这样
That's the Charter.
训练有素的探员
The most highly trained agents
在动荡的世界中 携手维护和平
working together to keep peace in a turbulent world.
不 这是子虚乌有的事
No. That is a Saturday morning cartoon.
没人了解特许局 因为他们不存在
Nobody knows about the Charter because they don't exist.
把醋递给我
Pass me the vinegar.
还有这女孩
-And this girl.
这女孩就是特许局的 你们心知肚明
This girl is part of it, and you know it.
好 别对我妄加评论 我就顺着你们的话说几句
Okay, don't judge me. I'm gonna go with this for a sec.
如果特许局喜欢帮倒忙
-If the Charter are such do-gooders… -Mm.
那女孩为何要打断我们的行动？
…why'd the girl interrupt our mission?
问得好 对
That's a good question. Yep.
不好意思 贝利
Sorry, Bailey.
没有什么隐秘的天才组织 在幕后操纵一切
There is no secret genius organization pulling all the strings.
只是我们、珊卓和她的文书工作
It's just us, Sandra, and her paperwork.
不过这个睡前故事不错
But it was a nice bedtime story.
说到这点…
Speaking of which…
怎么？你这就走了？
Already?
倒时差
Jet lag.
时差只有一小时
Um, there's a one-hour time difference.
晚安 各位
Night, guys.
-晚安 -晚安
-Night. -Night.
正中眼睛
Right in the eye.
-我用这只眼睛开车 -没准能让你车技更好
-I drive with that eye. -Might make you a better driver.
不可能让你车技更糟
Can't make you worse.
-开玩笑 我收回我的话 -不
-Kidding. I take it back. -No.
偷袭我？
Sneaking up on me?
外勤探员应随时准备应对任何情况
A field agent should be ready for anything.
你说什么？
You were saying?
真不该告诉你我会游泳
I never should have told you I swim.
一时心软
A weak moment.
我喜欢
I liked it.
所以…那个女孩
So… the girl.
有什么消息？
What news?
没有消息
No news.
上面交代过不要查
We were told not to look.
你真不会骗人
You're a terrible liar.
听着 如果这事交给军情六处的文员
Look, if we leave it to the pen-pushers at MI6,
在我们查到名字之前 她会骇遍全球
she'll hack the entire world before we even get a name.
我应该主动一点 把她抓过来的
I should've gone beyond the mission and brought her in.
你当时忙得不可开交
Well, your hands were pretty full at the time.
再说 我们的目标又不是抓她
And besides, it wasn't our objective.
尝试做点出格的事吧
Why don't you try and live a little?
可能会很好玩哦
Could be fun.
你不是叫我别下车吗？
What happened to "Don't get out of the van, Rachel"?
这不一样
-This is different. -Hm.
所以你无视规定时 就可以变通
So, rules are rules unless they apply to you.
看来你更了解我 而我不怎么了解你
Why do I feel like you know me better than I know you?
或许我该听听你那些无聊的播客
Maybe I should listen to one of these dreary podcasts of yours.
贝利影响到你了吧？
Bailey got to you, huh?
你再笑我们的音乐 我就不说自己的看法了
Mock our music, and I won't tell you my theory.
我会守口如瓶
My lips are sealed.
她是新手
She's new to the scene.
肯定是
Has to be.
否则我们会对她有所耳闻
Otherwise, we would have heard about her.
要搞到那样一份宾客名单…
To get a guest list like that--
她跟一名老手合作 不过是谁呢？
She's working with someone else. A veteran. But who?
我们列个名单出来 我会带零食过来
We'll make a list. I'll bring snacks.
抱歉 我已经跟人约了去吃早午餐
I, uh, I'm sorry. I already have… a brunch date.
我可以去吗？
Can I come?
再见 帕克
Bye, Parker.
（特许局：红心队总部）
艾沃？好久不见
Ivo? It's been a while.
红心九 很高兴见到你
Nine of Hearts, it's good to see you.
-还好吗？-一直在忙，- 这边
-How's it going? -It's been busy. This way.
特许局今早一直在处理 三起具有可行性的威胁
The Charter has been dealing with three actionable threats this morning.
巴黎可能会发生沙林毒气袭击
Potential sarin gas attack in Paris.
谍心预测了攻击时间和地点 有87%的把握
The Heart predicted the time and location of the attack with 87% certainty.
红心八现在在现场
Eight of Hearts is on site now.
红心六在中国南海
Six is defusing a potential international incident
化解一起潜在的国际事件
in the South China Sea.
方块队正在对付攻击北美电网的黑客
And Diamonds team's handling hackers targeting the North American power grid.
这就是那只孔雀
That, um… That's the peacock.
-你好 -随房附赠的
-Hi. -Came with the house.
嘿 杰克 喜欢你的新办公室吗？
-Hey, Jack.Enjoying your new office?
an't all be gallivanting around the Alps.
我们不可能都在阿尔卑斯山闲逛
We can't all be gallivanting around the Alps.
红心国王怎么样了？
How's King of Hearts?
她生气了？
Is she angry?
你见过她了？
Have you seen her yet?
我们来看看
Well, let's see.
场面失控
You lost control of the situation,
目标死亡 然后你不得不干掉六个人
Target is dead,then you had to kill six men.
战果辉煌 真该给你颁发维多利亚十字勋章
What a glorious outcome.-Victoria Crosses all around.
早安 诺玛
Morning, Nomad.
我也很高兴见到你
Good to see you too.
你把这地方改造得真不错
Love what you've done with the place.
她现在有幽默感了吗？
Is she developing a sense of humor?
找到那女孩了？
Did you find the girl?
当然
Of course.
凯娅达万
Keya Dhawan.
她是印度西部浦那的人
She is from Pune in the west of India.
八岁时沦为孤儿
Orphaned at eight.
她如何学会编程的？
How'd she learn to program?
听说过尼亚姆卡奇吗？
Ever heard of Niam Kharche?
制药业的亿万富翁投资人
Billionaire investor, pharmaceuticals.
他之前在浦那做生意
Had business in Pune.
为贫困社区的儿童开设IT学习营
Ran IT workshops for kids in underprivileged communities.
他在其中一个项目中发现了她
He spotted her in one of these programs.
对 他慧眼识珠
Yeah. He saw she was a prodigy.
把她纳入麾下 训练她
took her under his wing, trained her up.
后来他们闹翻了
and then they had a falling out.
为什么？
Why?
谍心擅长分析事实 分析原因是弱项
The Heart's better at whats than whys.
事实是 她与卡奇分道扬镳后 就人间蒸发了
And the what is, she split from Kharche and disappeared.
她今年22岁
She's 22 now.
我认识你时 也差不多是这个年纪
Not much older than when we met.
对 但她与不法之徒为伍
Yes, but she fell in with a bunch of criminal lowlifes.
有些人运气好
Some people get all the luck.
我们认为凯娅开设了血腥赌场
We think that Keya set up the casino of blood.
她深知穆菲尼有赌瘾 以此引他上钩
She knew about Mulvaney's gambling habit and used it to lure him in.
为什么？
Why?
穆菲尼迷上了一件 不一般的新武器
Mulvaney had become obsessed with a new weapon, a myth.
一台尖端量子计算机
A quantum computer sophisticated
可以入侵任何地方的任何东西
Enough to hack into anything, anywhere.
谍心
The Heart.
她现在身处何处？
So, where is she now?
谍心有96%的把握
The Heart predicts with 96% certainty
预测凯娅要去里斯本
That Keya is heading to Lisbon
参加莫里茨俱乐部的开业典礼
for the opening of Club Moritz.
我们会把她的位置透露给军情六处
So, we will leak her location to MI6.
然后24小时内 你们的行动就能重新启动
Then we should have your operation back up and running within 24 hours.
感觉不对劲
It doesn't feel right.
凯娅选择骇入我们在山上的通讯信号
Keya chose to hack into our comms feed on the mountain.
她主动跟我打招呼 直视我的眼睛
She revealed herself to me, looked me straight in the eye.
谍心是人类所拥有 最接近完美智能的系统
The closest mankind has to perfect intelligence,
我不确定 就因为她在酒吧里看了你一眼
Because of eye contact in a bar.
我们就该无视谍心的预测结果
We should just ignore the spy's predictions.
难怪你会单身 杰克
This might be why you're single, Jack.
依据预测结果行事吧
Just follow the numbers.
你的任务是去里斯本
Your mission is Lisbon.
如果她不在那里呢？
And if she's not there?
那就享用西班牙小菜
Eat tapas.
别跟你军情六处的队友吃就行
Just not with your MI6 team.
这么说你现在在监视我
So, you're spying on me now.
我在追踪麾下探员
I'm tracking my asset.
你清楚干这份活的条件
You know what you signed up for.
不准谈恋爱 不准交朋友
No relationships. No friends.
不准在泳池边跟人私聊
No poolside tête-à-tête.
我们的事业至关重要
What we do is too important.
政府失能时
When governments fail.
就只能靠特许局了
The only thing left is the Charter.
我是卧底 这是职责所在
I'm undercover. This is just part of it.
-一切尽在掌控中 -很好
-Everything's under control. -Good.
继续保持
Keep it that way.
你的目标是达万
Your target is Dhawan.
（关键词：“凯娅达万”）
（“凯娅达万”+“英国人来了”）
来吧 凯娅 上钩吧
Come on, Keya. Take the bait.
（未知用户聊天请求）
（接受）
（未知用户：找我吗？）
笑一个
Smile.
（现在是周五晚上 你没朋友吗？）
（你在赌场向我举杯 为什么？）
（我希望你们知道
自己擅闯了谁的派对）
（这不是游戏 凯娅）
（你想怎样？）
（你很快就知道了）
（未知用户：离线）
嘿 贝利
Hey, Bailey.
嘿 那个黑客女孩有线索了
Hey. We got a lead on hacker girl.
我们要去里斯本
We're going to Lisbon.
得找人帮你照顾猫了
Better call the cat sitter.
不用 巴里没事 它…
Oh no, no. Barry's all right. He's--
我告诉它了 不准开派对
I told him, no parties.
好了 做个好梦
Okay. Sweet dreams.
明早8点出发
Wheels up at eight.
知道了
Got it.
-晚安 贝利 -晚安
-Night, Bailey. -Night.
这个呢？
What about this?
老天 我们还以为情况不会变得更糟
Ah Jesus. Just when we thought it couldn't get worse.
-你在唱歌吗？帕克 你在唱歌吗？-没有 只是清嗓子
-Are you singing? -I'm clearing my throat.
歌曲
Tune.
-瞧瞧 -不
-Look at that. -No.
天籁之声
Voice of an angel.
（葡萄牙 里斯本）
你该认识一下我奶奶
Bailey, you should meet my gran.
她的音乐品位跟你一样
She has the same taste in music.
你们连发型都一样
and you have the same hair.
这是我的车 放什么歌我说了算
It's my van, my tunes.
对 她也这样说
Yeah, that's what she says.
不好意思
-Oh, sorry. -Whoa.
哇 下次再猛一点
Little harder next time.
我的牙没被磕掉
I didn't quite crack a tooth.
你还好吗？
You okay back there?
嗯 没事 我只是…
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just, uh…
-晕车 -嗯
-Carsick. -Mm.
贝利放的歌太难听了
-It's Bailey's music.
来吧 跟我换下座位
Come on, swap seats with me.
什么？不用 没事
What? No, no, no. It's fine.
来吧 不 没事 让开
Come on. No, it's fine. Move.
好
-Okay.
-老天！-安全带
-Jesus! -Seatbelt.
贝利！
Bailey!
你的车技不是应该很好吗？
Aren't you supposed to be an elite driver?
抱歉
Sorry.
-没事吧？-嗯
-Okay? -Yeah.
俱乐部还要多久才开张？
How long till the club opens?
我们几小时后出发
We head out in a couple of hours.
嘿 斯通
Hey, Stone.
给你发了个东西 看看吧
Sent you something. Check it out.
（维多利亚风手工娃娃屋）
-这是什么？-给我侄女的生日礼物
-What is this? -It's for my niece's birthday.
从女孩子的角度 你觉得怎么样？
What do you think? Female perspective?
超粉嫩的
It's very pink.
帕克 这音乐过时了
Parker, this music is ancient.
你是山顶洞人吗？
What are you, a hundred years old?
这叫文艺范
It's called culture.
嗯 抱歉 帕克 我跟小杨一个观点 小杨！
Yeah. Sorry, Parker, I'm with Yang. Yang!
太好了！
Yes!
-呜 -哦，好吧
-Woo! -Oh, okay.
这就对了
Now we're talking.
来啊 贝利 来嘛 别多想
Oh, come on, Bailey. You know you want to.
是的 我想
Yes, I do.
斯通？
Stone?
-太爽了 -斯通 来吧
-Oh yeah. Stone, come on.
来嘛 别多想 来吧
You know you want to. Come on.
好爽
Yeah.
不 不能走掉
Oh no you don't.
小心 你说不定会很开心
Watch out, you might actually enjoy yourself.
-她笑了 -太爽了！
-She's smiling. -Oh yeah!
六名敌人进入大楼…
Six hostiles entering the building…
九号 我们连上了
Nine, I have you.
六名敌人正在上楼 外面有更多
Six hostiles moving up the stairs. More outside.
他们即将破门而入 四…
They'll breach the doorway in four…
三
three…
二
two…
一
one.
帕克
Parker.
我会把你救出去
We're gonna get you out.
斯通 快走！
Stone, go now!
九号 窗户
Nine, the window.
马上出去
Get out. Now.
斯通 你会死的
Stone, you will die.
杰克 我需要你帮忙
Jack, I need your help.
规划撤离路线…开始
Plotting exit routes… now.
快 帕克 快醒醒
Come on. Parker, come on. Come on!
我要返回去
I'm going back in.
什么？不行
What? No.
你的任务不是救他们
Saving them is not your mission.
-快离开那里 -杰克 拜托
-Get out of there. -Jack, please.
不行 你重则没命 轻则暴露身份
No. At best, you break cover. Most likely, you die.
（信号丢失）
斯通？
Stone?
斯通！
Stone!
-老天 -快点
-Holy shit. -Come on.
该走了
Time to go.
还会有更多敌人 快点
There'll be more. Come on.
不能用车了 快走
Van's a no-go. Go, go.
那玩意管用吗？
Does that thing ever work?
对 管用 但不是对每辆车都管用
Yeah, yeah. It works. Just not on every car.
那里 快走！
There. Move!
斯通 别磨蹭了
Stone. Now would be good.
让开 让我来
Move over. I've got this.
避开枪 斯通 避开！
Away from the guns, Stone. Away!
稍等
Just a second.
趴下！
Down! Down! Down!
快追！
Go! Go, go, go, go!
好了 斯通 老实交代
Okay, Stone. Time to start talking.
你会黑客技术、身手不凡、车技了得 帕克 你懂吗？
You hack, you fight, and you drive. Parker, are you getting this?
-三辆车 很多枪 -嗯 子弹满天飞 看得出来
-Three vehicles. Lots of guns. -Yeah, I can tell by the bullets.
-斯通！-我忙着呢
-Stone! -Sort of in the middle of something.
哇 哦
Whoa!
踩刹车！刹车、刹车
Brakes, brakes, brakes!
Whoa!
好 算你牛逼
Oh, okay. Okay, you got it.
小杨
Yang.
-明白 -在你三点钟方向
-Got it. -On your three o'clock.
三、二、一
In three, two, one.
没子弹了
Clip's out.
你想让我们没命吗？
Are you trying to kill us?
恰恰相反
Pretty much the opposite, actually.
好了 这下可能会有点猛
Okay. This might be kind of intense.
情况不妙
Oh, this isn't good.
-斯通 敌人还是穷追不舍 -我知道
-Stone, they're still coming. -I know.
坐稳了
Hold on.
我不能代表其他人发言
Well, I can't speak for the others,
但我...我觉得你可以出外勤了
But I… I think you're ready for the field.
我们得驶离公路 把这辆车丢掉
We need to get off the road and lose this van.
瑞秋
Rachel.
斯通
Stone.
你到底是什么人？
Who the hell are you?
说来话长
It's complicated.
在我看来
-From where I'm sitting,
一名IT部门的菜鸟探员 干掉了一整支杀戮小队
a baby agent from IT just took out an entire kill team.
-拜托 贝利 你怎么一直蒙在鼓里？-该死
-Bailey, what's taking you so long? -Shit.
特许局？你是特许局的人？
The Charter? You're the… you're the bloody Charter?
怎么？你打算自己去抓达万吗？
What, are you trying to bring in Dhawan yourself?
你跟她是一伙的？
Are you working with her?
回答他
Answer him.
你欠我们一个答案
You owe us that.
我们也在追捕她
We're after her too.
我的天
Oh my God.
特许局真的存在
The Charter's real.
你是其中一员
And you're one of them.
听着 我没法透露太多
I wish I could've told you more.
但我们目标一致
But we all want the same thing.
不是这样的
No, we don't.
你不是唯一有秘密的人
You're not the only one with a secret.
你在乎他们吗？
Did they mean something to you?
别这样 瑞秋
Oh, come on, Rachel.
你只是在演戏 对吗？
You're only playing a part, right?
你是谁 帕克？
Who are you, Parker?
你何不问问谍心？
Why don't you ask the Heart?
如果你想要我的命 会最先冲我开枪
If you wanted me dead, you would have shot me first.
我还需要知道几件事
Still a few things I need to know.
关于你 关于特许局
About you, the Charter.
但或许最重要的是
But perhaps most of all,
我想打一架
I was looking forward to a fight.
说吧
-Talk.
凯娅和我得知 有特许局的人打入军情六处
Keya and I learned that the Charter infiltrated MI6.
我必须引蛇出洞
I had to flush out who.
起初我以为是小杨
At first, I thought it was Yang,
但我很高兴原来是你
but I was so pleased it was you.
凯娅是你的手下？
Keya's working for you?
你的手在发抖
Your hand's shaking.
你根本没刺伤我
You barely nicked me.
这才是重点
That was the point.
刀尖有毒药
Poison-tipped.
我知道只是雕虫小技 不过很管用
A little basic, I know, but it hits the spot.
看来麻醉剂开始起作用了
Looks like the paralysis is kicking in.
斯通 我花了六年的时间找你们
I spent six years looking for you people, Stone.
然后命运把你直接带到我面前
Then fate brings you straight to me.
你是一名出色的探员
You're a very good agent.
但你忙着让机器替你思考
But you were so busy letting a machine.
以致于没注意到我
Think for you that you missed me.
就在这里
Right here,
在你面前
in front of your face…
一直以来都在
the whole time.
那穆菲尼呢？
And Mulvaney?
他和我一样厌恶科技
Well, he was tech-averse like me.
只用脑子来记事
Kept everything up here.
于是我和凯娅设下血腥赌场 引他入局
So, Keya and I set up our casino of blood to lure him in.
我们需要谈谈谍心的事
We needed to have a little chat about the Heart.
好吧 好吧...
All right. Okay, okay, okay.
说吧
Talk.
好 我…
Yeah, I--
特许局的神通广大都是因为谍心
The Heart is what gives the Charter its power.
它是最令人生畏的武器 人们从来不知道它的存在
It's the most formidable weapon you never knew existed.
它可以入侵任何地方的任何东西
It can hack into anything, anywhere.
手机、电网、银行 政府、军方、健康档案
Cell phones, power grids, the banks, governments, military, health records.
你的秘密
Your secrets.
它比你更了解你自己
It knows you better than you know yourself.
其原理是决定论
It's determinism.
它可以同时访问数万亿个数据点
With access to trillions of data points at once,
模拟精准
Its modeling is so accurate.
可以预测未来
it can predict the future.
谍心就是知识和力量
The Heart is knowledge and power.
它可以让市场崩溃 也可以引发坠机
It can crash a market or drop a plane out of the sky.
如果能控制所有核弹
When you can control them all?
谁还需要偷呢？
Who needs to steal a nuclear bomb
拥有谍心
If you own the Heart…
就拥有了全世界
you own the world.
它在哪里？
Where is it?
Where… is it?
只有特许局的成员知道
Only a Charter member could tell you.
毒药是胆碱酯酶抑制剂
The poison's a cholinesterase inhibitor.
冷战时期的麻痹药
Cold War paralytic.
我的药剂师会调配各种经典毒药
My chemist does all the classics.
比如氰化物
Like cyanide.
放轻松 瑞秋
Oh, relax, Rachel.
我可不想杀你
Killing you is not part of the plan.
我们需要你先去送个包裹
We need you to deliver a package first.
很高兴跟你共事 瑞秋
-I've loved working with you, Rachel.
我扪心发誓
Hand on heart.
斯通？
Stone?
她醒了 她醒了
She's awake. She's awake.
按住 按住她
Hold her here. Hold her down.
哦 该死
Oh shit.
拿着 帮帮我 帮我一把
-Take this. Help me. Help me here.
别让她动弹
Keep her steady.
胆碱…胆碱酯…
Cholinest-- Cholines--
等等 给我五毫升阿托品
Wait. Get me atropine. Five mils.
是胆碱酯酶
It's cholinesterase.
杰克
Jack. Jack.
-有人入侵 -怎么会？
-We've been breached. -How?
我们的系统里 有个无线发送的木马病毒
It's… There's a Trojan in our system delivered wirelessly.
它在肆无忌惮地攻击我们的安全系统
Chewing through security like it isn't there.
禁止所有访问权限
Restrict all access.
诺玛 我试过了 不行 他们试图访问谍心
Nomad, I've tried. No-go. They're trying to access the Heart.
从哪里来的？我们有防火墙
From where? We're walled off.
是个微弱的无线信号 来自…
It's a weak wireless signal. It's coming from…
大楼内部
inside the building.
斯通
Stone.
快点 我们需要监视她的气管
Quickly. We need to monitor her airway.
-开始吧 -按住她
-Go ahead. -Hold her.
按下去
Press down.
你在干什么？
That didn't do it.
斯通
Stone.
怎么了？我要知道发生了什么事
What's happened? I need to know what's happened.
我们被入侵多久了？
How long were we compromised?
3分45秒 正在运行系统检查
Three minutes and 45 seconds. Running a system check now.
我们得知道他们访问了哪些资料 谍柜安全吗？
We need to know what they accessed. Is the Locker safe?
谍柜还在高空飞行
The Locker is still flying high
离地面26千米 谍心在里面安全无虞
with the Heart safe inside, 85,000 feet up.
没有航天飞机，谁也上不去
No one's getting up there without a space shuttle.
它正飞越大西洋 向西非进发
It's passing over the Atlantic, towards West Africa.
其他团队还能访问谍心吗？
And the other suits, can they still access the Heart?
-看来可以  -老天
-Looks like it-- Jesus.
怎么？
What?
尝试访问文件的次数已达十万次
There've been 100,000 attempts to access files.
梅花队正在分析数据 不过看来我们的安全措施没被攻破
Clubs team are analyzing the data, but looks like our security held.
我们必须马上把它关闭
We need to shut it all down now.
关闭什么？谍心？
Shut what down? The Heart?
我们得先知道他们做了什么
Until we know what they've done.
我们不知道他们有什么能耐
We have no idea what they're capable of.
但要弄清楚他们做了什么 没必要关闭谍心
Don't need to shut it down to find out what they've done.
这样对我们自己不利
We'd be harming ourselves.
这可不一定 她不傻
We don't know. She's not stupid.
-我们也不傻 -确定吗？因为现在…
-And neither are we. -Sure about that? Because right now--
瑞秋 他说得对 我们会解决
Rachel. Rachel. He's right. We'll sort it.
“我们”？
"We"?
我要跟你私下谈谈 马上过来
A word in private. Now.
我早就说了
I told you.
我就知道凯娅在耍我们 在玩弄谍心
I knew Keya was playing us, playing the Heart.
不 你不知道 只是你的感觉
No, you didn't. No, you didn't You had a feeling.
没确凿证据 也没可执行方案
Nothing… nothing concrete, nothing actionable.
情绪、观念、预感 都是胡扯 这些东西我们不买账
A mood, a notion, a hunch, a bollocks. We don't trade in those.
我就知道她不会去
I knew she wouldn't be there.
你无视谍心 折回去
You ignored the Heart, and you went back in.
-我是为了救队友 -他们不是你的队友
-To save my team. -They weren't your team.
他们还是死了 你折回去 害他们必死无疑
They died anyway. You going back made sure of that.
你暴露了身份
You blew your cover.
如果你照我们的指示离开 帕克就不会追踪你
If you'd left when we told you to, Parker would've followed you,
我们就会抓到他 小杨和贝利或许还活着
we'd have caught him, and Yang and Bailey might be alive.
那么我就该听从谍心？
I should've just listened to the Heart?
是的
Yes.
特许局的存在只为一个原因
The Charter exists for one reason.
最大限度地挽救生命 这是唯一的道德标准
To maximize lives saved. That's the only moral metric there is.
这是计算 纯粹而客观的计算
And it's a calculation. A pure and objective calculation.
让一台机器为我们计算
Made for us by a machine.
你忘了那有多重要吗？0
Have you forgotten how radical that is?
这并不意味着 我们所做之事很容易或感觉很好
It doesn't mean that what we do is easy or feels nice.
在你的余生中 这些人的声音都会萦绕在你脑海里
You'll have the voices of those people in your head for the rest of your life.
你永远会觉得自己害死了他们
And you will never not feel responsible for them ever.
但为达目的 不择手段
But the end justifies the means.
一年来 我跟帕克每天共处
I spent every day with Parker for a year
没料到会这样
And didn't see it coming.
对
No.
谍心也没预测到
Neither did the Heart.
我们现在该怎么办？
So, what do we do now?
我…
I'm…
要做一些艰难的抉择 这是第一个
Gonna make some tough choices, and this is the first one.
你被解职了 瑞秋
I'm standing you down, Rachel.
回家好好休息
Go home. Get some rest.
保持低调 别做傻事
Keep your head down. Don't do anything stupid.
你不能这样
You can't do this.
你已经暴露了
You're compromised.
帕克知道你 达万也知道
Parker knows you. Dhawan knows you.
其他国王不知道能否信任你 这也情有可原
And the other Kings, quite rightly… don't know if you can be trusted.
那你呢？
And you?
我想保护我们花了20年打造的东西
I want to protect what we've spent 20 years trying to build.
所以我就这样出局了
So, I'm just out.
这是为大局着想
It's about the greater good.
不是针对你
It's nothing personal.
对的
No.
我开始明白这点了
I'm starting to see that.
（还想玩）
喂？
Hello?
-斯通？打错了 -是找我的
-Stone? Wrong number. Wait. -It's for me.
那是我的手机 我…
That's my phone. I--
一位特许局探员在中毒数小时后
So, why is a Charter agent riding around all alone,
为何独自搭巴士四处游荡？
just hours after being poisoned?
他们好像不在乎自己最重要的探员
Doesn't feel like they're taking care of their most valuable player.
你想怎样？
What do you want?
不要输不起
Don't be a sore loser.
你以前一定觉得我俩很像
I bet you used to think we were so alike.
现在你知道我更胜一筹
Now you know I'm better.
更胜一筹？
Better?
你杀了我的朋友
You killed my friends.
什么？
What?
你不知道吗？
You didn't know, huh?
我告诉过你这不是游戏 凯娅
Well, I told you this wasn't a game, Keya.
不管有没有谍心
Heart or no Heart,
我都不会放过你
I'm coming for you.
-早安 长官 -早安
-Morning, ma'am. -Morning.
诺玛 这地方不错
Nomad. Great spot.
四国王齐聚一堂 多久没这样了？
All four kings in the same room. How long has it been,
三年？
Three years?
还不够久
Not long enough.
这位帕克是何许人？
So, who is this Parker,
我们怎么会没有识破他？
And how did we miss him?
专职情报员 生于贝尔法斯特 独居
Career intelligence agent. Born in Belfast,
他无亲无故
lives alone.
无牵无挂 他…
He has no one he cares for. There's nothing much to live for.
精忠报国 却被国家视如草芥
He has devoted his life to a country that sees him as expendable.
好吧 我们明白
Okay. We get it. All that is fuel for the fire.
这一切都是火上浇油
但没有火星子也烧不起来
-But it won't burn without a spark.
我刚刚正要说这点
I was getting to that.
我迫不得已 对一些老朋友施压
I had to lean extremely hard on some very old friends for this.
才拿到这个
Just got this.
车臣共和国 2015年12月
Chechnya, December 2015.
这是什么？
What's this?
是你加入之前的事 甚至在谍心问世之前
It was before your time. Before the Heart, for that matter.
车臣和俄罗斯政府 任由一位车臣军阀为所欲为
A Chechen warlord was given free rein by the Chechen and Russian governments.
西方国家一如既往 视而不见
The West, as always, were looking the other way.
他扫荡了无数村庄
He was wiping out whole villages,
消除异己
Trying to stamp out dissent.
但这跟帕克有何关系？
But… what's this got to do with Parker?
他当时在场
He was there.
用的是另一个身份 没有电子记录
Different identity. No electronic records.
但他当时在场 跟军情六处一起
But he was there, with MI6,
运送武器 以消灭那个军阀
delivering weapons to take the warlord out.
看到他们了吗？
Any sign of them?
预计要多久？
You got an ETA yet?
他们很快就到
They'll be here.
我们拦截了一则通讯
We intercepted a communication.
那是个陷阱
It was a trap.
从军情六处传来情报
Intelligence came through from MI6 that
说他们整支队伍都被处决了
That their entire team had been executed.
我们以为无人生还
We thought there was no one left to save.
那个地区情势危急
The region was a tinderbox
随时可能爆发全面内战
On the verge of full civil war.
我们不能让那些武器落入军阀之手
We couldn't let those weapons fall into the warlord's hands.
这将导致成千上万人丧生
It would have cost thousands of lives.
我们在空中
We had a drone.
有一架携带导弹的无人机
That was stationed overhead armed with missiles.
是我亲自下令的
I gave the order myself.
我们让人误以为 这起无人机袭击是叛军发动的
We made it look like a rebel force had ordered the drone strike.
军情六处将自己的过失雪藏起来
MI6 buried their mistake.
没有报告 没有调查
No report, no investigation.
没有相关人员的记录
No record of the personnel who had been involved.
我们以为所有人都死了
We thought everyone had died.
直到几小时前
Until a few hours ago.
真是一团糟
What a mess.
这么说 你认为
So, you think…
他知道当初是我们干的？
He knows it was us?
这个推断比较合理
I think that's a safe assumption.
现在他要摧毁特许局
And now he wants to destroy the Charter.
你杀了贝利和小杨？
You killed Bailey and Yang?
这不在计划内
That wasn't the plan.
你只管技术 战略的事交给我 好吗？
You stick to the tech and leave strategy to me, okay?
提醒你一下 我们是搭档 好吗？
Let me remind you, we're partners. Okay?
如果你希望我好好做事
So if you want me to do my job,
就得在动手之前 提前通知我
you have to tell me what you're doing before you do it.
我提醒你一下
Let me remind you.
特许局根本不在乎贝利和小杨这种人
The Charter don't give two shits about people like Bailey and Yang.
你若希望我们成功
So, if you want us to succeed,
也不该在乎
you shouldn't either.
嘿 巴里
Hey, Barry.
我是你爸的朋友
I'm a friend of your dad's.
没事的
It's okay.
有我在呢
I've got you.
（笑一个！）
摄像头
The camera.
她黑入摄像头信号
She hacked into the camera feed.
来看看她的隐身技术有多高明
Let's see how well she covered her tracks.
找到了
There she is.
凯娅 你去沙漠干什么？
What's in the desert, Keya?
那里可没什么夜生活可言
I'm guessing it's not the nightlife.
开什么玩笑？
Are you shitting me?
西非 谍柜
West Africa. The Locker.
你以前做过这种事吗？
You ever done this before?
在12千米的高空开直升机？
Choppered in at over 40,000 feet?
你诓我呢 没人干过那种事
Trick question. No one has.
但我妈妈总是说
But my mama always said,
我无所不能
I could do anything.
谍柜还要多久才会降落？
How long do we have before the Locker descends?
11小时零7分钟
Eleven hours and seven minutes.
到那时 特许局就会恍然大悟
At which point, the Charter will realize what's going on.
谍柜降落至12千米的高空 需要9分26秒
It'll take nine minutes and 26 seconds for the Locker to drop to 40,000 feet.
我们有约八分钟的时间 可以进去 夺走谍心
We'll have about eight minutes to get in, take the Heart,
然后在他们重获控制之前离开
and get out again before they regain control.
非常精准
Very precise.
你确定吗？
You're sure?
不确定 谍柜降落时我才能确定
No. I'll be sure when it descends.
我的代码若被发现 谍柜就不会降落
If they found my code, it won't descend,
我们会落入他们的网中 然后死翘翘
They'll be waiting for us, and we all die.
嘿
Hey.
早上好
Good morning.
现在几点了？
What time is it?
快7点了
Uh, it's nearly seven.
什么？该死
What? Oh shit.
有进展吗？
Any luck?
没有 不过他们迟早会现身的
Uh… nothing. But they need to pop their heads up at some point.
我会看看他们是否…
-I'll see if they--
糟糕 不，不...
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
马上叫诺玛过来！
Get Nomad now! Get Nomad now!
送我上去
Just get me up there.
剩下的事交给我
I'll do the rest.
诺玛肯定不会放过我
Nomad will string me up for this.
告诉她是我偷了你的钥匙
Tell her I stole your keys.
相信我就好
You'll just have to trust me.
好 关键时刻到了
Okay. Moment of truth.
我们如何知道是否成功了？
How will we know if it's worked?
快看
Would you look at that?
在过去两分钟内 谍柜下降了将近4.6千米
The Locker has been dropped 15,000 feet in the last two minutes.
还在继续降落
Still descending.
安全系统都已失效 我被锁在外面了
Security systems are all down. I'm locked out.
怎么可能？我们又被入侵了？
How is that even possible? Another hack?
不 他们第一次入侵 就是为了这个目的
No. No.This is why they did it the first time.This is why they did it the first time.
它一直潜伏在我们的系统内 直到现在
It's been lying dormant in our system until now.
-能覆盖掉吗？-我正在努力
-Can you override it? -I'm trying.
气闸舱遭到入侵
The air lock's been breached.
联络这一带所有特许局探员
Contact every Charter agent in the region.
800公里范围内没人
There's no one within 500 miles.
正在接近坐标 五、四、三…
Approaching coordinates in five, four, three--
-真希望你知道自己在做什么 -我也希望
-I hope you know what you're doing. -Tell me about it.
有东西在快速靠近我们
We have a something approaching fast.
东西？
A something?
-30秒后抵达 -是什么？
-Thirty seconds out. -What is it?
我想…我想是一个人
I think-- I think it's a someone.
是谁？
Who is it?
放大一点
Go in closer.
那是…
Is that--?
是斯通
It's Stone.
我得降低高度 降低旋翼转速
I have to descend. Lower the rotor speed.
收到 七分钟后见
Copy that. See you in seven minutes.
她没法及时赶到
She's not gonna make it.
-呜
-Woo!
瞧瞧是谁来了
Look who it is.
-我需要一点时间 -不行！
-I'm gonna need a minute. -No!
飞船上充满了氢气 来一个火星子 我们就死定了
The ship's lining is filled with hydrogen. One spark, and we're all dead.
没办法联系上她
No way to get hold of her.
加油 瑞秋
Come on, Rachel.
加油
Come on.
结束了 凯娅
It's over, Keya.
对谁来说？
For who?
我叫你别出外勤
I told you not to get out of the van.
你也叫我找点乐子
You also told me to have some fun.
没了
It's gone.
（谍心）
（管理员已锁定为凯娅达万）
现在你得听我的了
And now you answer to me.
我们失去谍心了
We've lost the Heart.
还没有
Not yet.
帕克 还有90秒 走吧
Parker. Ninety seconds. Let's go.
你的降落伞坏了 真可惜 你会需要的
Shame about your parachute. You'll be needing that.
放开我！
Get off me!
不！
No, no, no, no, no!
去追她们
不可能 照这个情况 我们能飞到基地就算走运了
-Get after them. -Impossible.
别过来！
Get away!
别烦我！
Leave me alone!
早安 美女
Morning, sunshine.
把东西交给我 免得有人…
Give me that thing before somebody gets--
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
那么，接下来会发生什么？
So, here's what's gonna happen.
你施展大探员的浑身解数 带我们回到文明世界
You're gonna secret-agent our way back to civilization,
我拿着这把枪跟在后面 距离三步之遥
and I'm gonna follow three steps behind you with this gun.
-谍心在哪里？-在帕克手上
-Where's the Heart? -Parker has it.
但我用我的生物特征给它加密了 没有我 那玩意就没用
But I encrypted it to my biometrics, so it's useless without me.
快点 起来
Come on, get up.
如果我现在对你开枪 一切就结束了
If I shoot you now, all this is over.
像你对贝利和小杨那样 毫不心慈手软
Show you the same mercy you showed Bailey and Yang.
那样做合情合理 瑞秋
It's the logical play, Rachel.
谍心也会让你这样做 对吧？
It's what the Heart would tell you to do.
我跟你不一样
I'm not like you.
站起来
On your feet.
我们得继续走
We need to keep moving.
（塞内加尔 隆普尔沙漠）
你有何计划 凯娅？
So, what's the plan, Keya?
想报复尼亚姆卡奇吗？
Trying to get even with Niam
是他把你赶出家门的
Kharche for kicking you out of the penthouse?
对 你自以为无所不知
Right. You think you know everything.
谍心一定告诉过你 他收养了我
I bet the Heart told you that he adopted me,
让我摆脱贫困 但它告诉你原因了吗？
lifted me out of nothing. But did it tell you why?
卡奇把我父母当成医学实验的小白鼠
Kharche used my parents like lab rats in a medical trial,
害死了他们
And it killed them.
他掩盖整件事 收养我 自以为是帮我
He covered everything up and took me in thinking he was doing me a favor,
但我让他那样认为
but I let him think.
因为我知道总有一天 我会强大起来
That because I knew one day.I'd be strong enough
让他为我父母的死付出代价
To make him pay for what he did to my parents.
所以你要摧毁整个世界？
So, you get to tear the whole world down?
我不只是为了自己
Oh, this is not just for me.
是为了像我一样的人
It's for people like me.
帕克要毁了特许局
Parker's gonna destroy the Charter.
我拿到了恶人名单 我们要让他们全部曝光
I've got my whole naughty list, and we're going to expose them all.
不计后果
With no thought of what comes next.
你真幼稚
You're a child.
你以为特许局就好很多吗？
And you think the Charter's any better?
他们救了你 这不代表他们就是好人
Just because they saved you doesn't make them good.
你以为我没查过你吗？
You think I didn't look into you?
你被多少所学校开除过？
How many schools did you get kicked out of?
七所？
Seven?
八所？
Eight?
总是叛逆不羁 总是惹麻烦
Always a rebel. Always a problem.
-暴力、独孤、无助 -够了
-Violent, alone, helpless. -Stop.
直到特许局出现 对吧？
-Until the Charter comes along, right?
给了你渴望已久的约束
And gives you that discipline that you so clearly crave.
但他们收留你是因为你优秀吗？
But did they take you in because you were good?
-还是因为你是个残次品？-够了
-Or because you were broken? -Enough.
或许我曾经是个残次品
Maybe I was broken.
但我知道一个叫诺玛的女人
But there's a woman I know only as Nomad.
她救了我 训练我
She rescued me, trained me,
让我知道如果有人罩着你
showed me what's possible when there's someone watching your back.
可能性会无穷无尽
The possibilities are endless.
她现在在哪里？
Where is she now?
走吧
Let's go.
帕克会来找你
Parker's coming for you,
我得有把更大的枪来对付他
And I wanna have a bigger gun when he shows up.
他们朝我们这边来了
They're headed for us.
或许是帕克
Maybe it's Parker.
肯定不是特许局
It's definitely not the Charter.
雇佣兵？
Mercenaries?
好 编个故事骗他们吧
Okay, let's just, um, give them a good cover story.
为了赎金 他们会留我们一命
They'll keep us alive for ransom.
引他们上钩 然后给他们个痛快
We reel them in, and then bam.
话说清楚“给他们个痛快”就是你把他们干掉
Just to be clear, the "bam" is for you to take them out.
嗯 我明白
Yeah, I get that.
你们是什么人？
Who are you people?
究竟来这里做什么？
What the hell are you doing here?
要搭车吗？
Need a ride?
你真是太好了
That's very kind of you.
特许局可以把卡奇干掉
The Franchise Board can take out Karchy.
帕克并非你唯一的出路
Parker is not your only way out.
我们要怎样报答你？
你们已经报答了
How can we ever repay you?
跟我来
Come with me.
她逃跑了
She got away.
之前的约定不是这样的
That wasn't the deal.
我们也没说要杀她
Killing her wasn't the deal either.
你现在得付钱给我
You have to pay me now.
交易改变了
The deal changed.
你可真难找
You're a hard woman to find.
红心六
Six of Hearts.
诺玛让我向你问好
Nomad sends her best.
达万跟帕克会合了
Dhawan is back with Parker.
我给她偷偷装了个追踪器
I slipped her a tracker.
他们正往北走 我把他们的信号分享给你
They're heading north. Looping you in now.
你好 瑞秋
Hi, Rachel.
很高兴听到你的声音
Nice to hear your voice.
我之前有点担心你
I was a bit worried about you.
是吗？
Were you?
好 找到她了 他们正前往冰岛
Okay, got her. They're heading towards Iceland.
我现在已经没有危险了吧？
I take it I'm no longer compromised.
谍心在他们手上 所以现阶段 我们都有危险
Well, they have the Heart, so we're all compromised.
帕克的目标是特许局 我们要去一个安全地点
Parker's coming after the Charter, so we're heading to a secure location.
梅花正在组队
Clubs is assembling a team.
我们会确保他们比你提前到达
We'll make sure they're on the ground by the time you arrive.
要是我们赶不及呢？
And if we're too late?
尽快赶到那里就行
Just get there as fast as you can.
若是他们让谍心上线
If they get the Heart online,
天知道他们能做出什么事
God knows what they're capable of.
我这就出发
I'm on my way.
这里并非坚不可摧
It's not impregnable,
但没有更好的地方了
but it's the best we've got.
如果谍心想找到我们 它会成功
If the Heart wants to find us, it will.
这破烂玩意能飞到冰岛吗？
Will this hunk of junk make it to Iceland?
当然能
Hell yeah.
（冰岛 奈斯亚威里尔）
你昨天给谍心加了人脸识别 真不错
Nice trick you pulled with the facial recognition yesterday.
给我们的新玩具加上一道锁
Trying to put a lock on our new toy.
要是我不那样做 你会回来救我吗？
Would you come back for me if I hadn't?
我们是队友 凯娅
We're a team, Keya.
下不为例
Don't do it again.
我应该查到了
I think I have it.
我知道他们要去哪里
I know where they're going.
雷克雅未克大学计算机实验室
Reykjavik University computer lab.
那里有个低温储存设施
It has a cryo-storage facility,
好几层楼的服务器
several floors of servers.
追踪器正朝着那个方向过去
The tracker's heading straight for it.
看吧 凯娅 别说我不守信用
See, Keya, don't say I don't keep my promises.
好了 做好准备
Okay, be ready.
各位都清楚指示
You know your instructions.
几分钟后 就可以上线运行
Couple of minutes, we'll be up and running.
上线了吗？
Are we up?
上线了
We're up.
这就是你的恶人名单？
Is this your naughty list?
电邮、短信、银行账户
Emails, texts, bank accounts.
谍心利用我的算法筛查了一切信息
The Heart's using my algorithm to sort through it all.
所以我们能找到任何人？访问任何东西？
So, we can find anyone? Gain access to anything?
全世界最棒的万能密钥
Greatest skeleton key in the world.
给我看看
Show me.
有了
There it is.
多年来 卡奇在全国各地的 无辜人士身上做实验 这是证据
Evidence of Kharche's years of experiments on innocents across the country.
这是世人都该有目共睹的真相
That's the truth… for the world to see.
真厉害
That's impressive.
不过看看这玩意还能做什么
But let's see what else this thing can do.
帮我把国王都找出来
Find me the Kings.
你要做什么？
What are you doing?
南茜莫里森
Nancy Morrison.
方块国王 前中情局探员
King of Diamonds. Ex-CIA.
谍心显示
The Heart tells us.
她正带着家人前往安全屋
Tells us she's heading to a safe house with her family.
让电梯坠落
Drop the lift.
你没开玩笑吧？
Are you serious?
不 别…
No. Do--
不客气
You're welcome.
等等 我还有个发现
Hang on. I have another one.
-你应该会喜欢 -什么？
I think you're gonna like this, boss.
一架身份不明的军用飞机
An unidentified military plane landed
33分钟前在一个私人机场降落
at a private airfield 33 minutes ago.
那里
There.
徐江 在中国国安部工作了35年
Jiang Hsu. Served 35 years in Chinese State Security Service.
梅花国王就在冰岛
The King of Clubs is here in Iceland.
那更好 他现在在哪里？
Even better. Where is he now?
我们两分钟后到
Two minutes out.
正在发送计划 斯通在路上了
Sending the plans now. Stone is on her way.
我们没时间等了
We don't have time to wait.
告诉她跟着我们就行
Tell her to follow us in.
有黑桃队和红心队的消息吗？
Any news of Spades or Hearts?
还没有
Nothing yet.
那架电梯和那个大厅里还有其他人
There were other people in that elevator. In that lobby.
冷静 凯娅
Calm down, Keya.
你说我们要让卡奇曝光
You said we were going to expose Kharche.
然后是特许局
and then the Charter,
而不是杀了他们
not murder them.
红心国王跟她的团队在一起
The King of Hearts with her team.
他们在伦敦郊外的地堡里
They're in a bunker outside of London.
很好
Good.
把他们干掉
Take them out.
我们马上就到了
We're approaching now.
-后会有期 -你要跟他们一起进去？
-We'll see you on the other side. -You're going in with them?
是我下令袭击帕克的
I ordered the strike on Parker.
这样才公平
It's only fair.
你知道
You know…
如果当年我在车臣 也会那样做
I would have made the same call in Chechnya.
多谢 那是正确的…
Thanks. The right--
断线了
I've lost contact.
谍心上线了
The Heart's online.
不
No, no, no, no.
我们被锁在里面了
We're locked in.
老天 他们把我们的通风系统关掉了
Oh God. They've shut off our ventilation system.
不
No, no, no, no.
（氧气）
杰克 我们还有多少时间？
Jack, how long we got?
照这个速度
At this rate,
大概一小时后 氧气就会耗尽
About an hour and we're out of oxygen.
特许局总是毫不犹豫清除绊脚石
The Charter never worries about who gets in their way.
我们也不会多想
Neither will we.
红心国王被锁起来了 一小时后 他们就会没命
King of Hearts is locked in. They'll be dead in an hour.
你不能继续这样 拜托
You have to stop this, please.
这种权力必须有人来掌控 凯娅
Someone has to control this power, Keya.
-我们就担此重任吧 -之前不是这样说的
-Why not us? -This is not what we agreed.
你还是没从大局出发
You're still not seeing the bigger picture.
你对杀害双亲的仇人不满
This isn't about some pissy little grievance you had
重点与这个无关
That's not the point.
重点是权力
This is about power.
权力集中在少数人手中
Concentrated in the hands of the few,
少数能用权力来做好事的人
Of the very few who could use it for good,
他们可以做出改变 但他们不那样做
who could actually make a change, but they don't.
此刻 我们正在挖掘数万亿条数据
At this moment, we are mining trillions of pieces of data.
再过几小时
In a matter of hours,
我就能干掉特许局剩余的成员
I will be able to take down the remaining members of the Charter.
我们这辈子一直任人利用和摆布
We've been used and manipulated our whole lives.
现在该由我们来控制一切了
Now it's time for us to take control.
（雷克雅未克大学）
快
Go.
梅花队已进入校区大楼了
Clubs team are inside the university building.
你在做什么？
What… are you doing?
凯娅 想知道伟人如何获得权力吗？
You wanna know how great men get power, Keya?
他们不是靠努力争取
It's not because they earn it…
也不是名至实归
or because they deserve it.
是因为时机来临时
It is because when the moment comes,
他们顺势夺权
they take it.
斯通一分钟后到
Stone is one minute out.
就位 我们都准备好了
In position. We're all set.
她快到大学了
She's approaching the university.
（已开始上传）
斯通 你得马上离开
Stone, you need to get out now.
我没时间了
I don't have long.
凯娅？
Keya?
我在上传故障保险 它会让谍心失效
I have a failsafe uploading. It will disable the Heart.
没有我 他们就不能访问它
They won't be able to access it without me.
我在外面 但你已经知道了
I'm outside. But you already know that.
不 不行 这是陷阱
No, you're not. It's a trap.
我找到你的追踪器了
I found your tracker.
那个实验室是个诱饵
The lab is a decoy.
你得让你的队友马上离开
You need to get your team out now.
-我凭什么相信你？-因为你说得对
-Why should I believe you? -Because you were right.
好吧 你告诉我帕克的事
Okay? You told me about Parker,
都被你说中了 瑞秋
and you were right about everything.
我的父母绝不希望我这样
My parents would have never wanted this.
请你听我说
Just please listen to me.
让你的队友马上离开
Get your team out of there right now.
-告诉我你在哪里 -好
-Tell me where you are. -Okay.
我把我的坐标发给你 我会让后门开着
I'm sending you my coordinates. I'll leave the back door open.
该死
Shit.
我是红心九 我需要你的对讲机
I'm Nine of Hearts. I need your radio.
快走
Go.
我是红心九
This is Nine of Hearts.
快出来 是陷阱
Get out of there. It's a trap.
你们听到了吗？她发现追踪器了 快出来
Do you hear me? She found the tracker. Get out of there.
你们听到了吗？
Do you hear me?
嗯 我听到你的话了
Yeah… I hear you.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
她在哪里？
Where is she?
她做了什么？
What has she done?
要多久才能修复？
-How long to fix it? -Oh.
我…可能几分钟 可能几小时
I-- Could be minutes. Could be hours.
我回来之前把它修好
You have until I get back.
门打不开
The door won't move.
可恶！
Damn it!
肯定是有应急覆盖系统
There must be an emergency override system.
我们一定是遗漏了什么
We must have missed something.
杰克 我们有办法联系上斯通吗？
Jack, is there any way we can get hold of Stone?
不 没有通讯 我们仍处于离线状态
No. No comms. We're still offline.
要不…要不试试座机吧
Maybe-- Maybe try the landline.
好
Okay. Okay.
斯通 谢天谢地 你在哪里？
Stone, thank God. Where are you?
梅花队的人死了
Clubs are dead.
大学是个陷阱
University was a trap.
我有新情报
I have new intel.
新地点
A new location.
梅花队的人都死了？
We've-- We've lost Clubs?
什么新情报？
What new intel?
凯娅 她把谍心关闭了
Keya. She shut down the Heart.
你如何知道她没耍你？
How do you know she's not playing you?
我不知道
I don't.
不到一小时 我们就会死
We're gonna die in less than an hour.
-他们关闭了我们的通风系统 -什么？
-They shut down our air supply. -What?
她关闭了我们的通风系统
She shut down our air supply.
是帕克干的
Parker did.
我相信她 诺玛
I believe her, Nomad.
要不是听了她的话 我也没命了
I'd be dead too if I hadn't listened to her.
我相信她 你得相信我
I trust her, and you need to trust me.
50分钟
Fifty minutes.
应该没问题
I can work with that.
再会
I'll see you.
You too.
抱歉 我要借用你的卡车
Sorry, I need your truck.
我知道你在里面 凯娅
I know you're in here, Keya.
你还有选择的机会
You know, you still have a choice.
你仍然可以参与其中
You can still be a part of this.
事情无可避免 你只是在拖延而已
You're only delaying the inevitable.
-你要我等着吗？-千万别等
-Would you like me to wait? -Definitely no.
不过谢了！
But thanks!
拜托 凯娅
Come on, Keya.
（氧气）
冷静下来
Settle down now.
节省氧气
Conserve air.
快走
-Move.
让谍心重新上线
Get the Heart back online.
快点！
Do it!
起来
Get up.
起来！
Get up!
好 我们从哪里开始？
Right. Where do we start?
手指？
Fingers?
不行 手指还有用 膝盖？
No, we'll be needing those. Knees?
好
-Yeah.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
好 我做就是了
Okay, I'll do it.
去吧
Go on.
我得回去那里
I need to get back in there.
必须把谍心断开连接 然后再重新连接到服务器上
The Heart has to be disconnected and reconnected again to the servers.
有任何干扰
Any interference,
系统就会自动关闭 你知道的
the system automatically shuts down. You know that.
走
Move.
你不会有好下场的  斯通
This doesn't end well for you, Stone.
你往前一步 她就死定了
Take another step, and she's dead.
我不在乎 我的目标是你
I don't care. I'm here for you.
胡扯
Bullshit.
你我都清楚 没有她
You and I know that without this one,
谍心就无法重新上线
the Heart stays down
地堡里的所有人都会死
and everyone inside that bunker dies,
当然 除非他们已经死了
unless, of course, they're dead already.
谍心在我手上
I have the Heart,
几位国王也在我手上 我赢定了
And I have the Kings. That's a winning hand.
好 我把枪放下
Okay. I'll put it down.
好样的
Good girl.
把枪踢开
Now, kick it away.
不过跟我说说
Tell me this, though.
你到底想怎样？
What's your point, hm?
你为何非要杀死他们不可？
And why do you have to kill them to make it?
瑞秋 我为国效命一辈子 结果一切皆枉然
I've served my entire life, Rachel, and none of it mattered.
世界依然混乱不堪
The world is still in chaos.
谍心有能力改变一切
The Heart has the power to change everything.
但 特许局却用它来保持现状
But the Charter are using it to keep things exactly as they are.
你并不想改变任何东西
You don't wanna change anything.
只是想当老大而已
You just wanna be the one in charge.
你一掌权 就大开杀戒
First thing you did with all that power was kill people.
帕克 你这种人有个问题
The problem with men like you, Parker,
那就是你们的权力 永远只建立在威胁和暴力之上
is that your power is only ever based on threats and violence.
当你残忍对待身边所有人
And when you brutalize everyone.
连自己的队友都不放过时
around you, even your own team…
你绝不会拥有一样东西 而我知道我会永远拥有它
you'll never have the one thing I know I always will.
是吗？
Yeah?
是什么 瑞秋？
And what is that, Rachel?
有人会罩着我
Someone to watch my back.
下辈子吧
Maybe in the next life.
那到时候见
See you when I get there.
诺玛 告诉我你没事
Nomad, tell me you're okay.
大家都还活着吗？
Is everyone still with us?
是的
Yeah, yeah.
很高兴听到你的声音 斯通
It's good to hear from you, Stone.
我就知道你会成功
I knew I would.
（四周后）
嘿 巴里
Hey, Barry.
这是什么？
What's this?
不知道
I don't know.
好漂亮
It's beautiful.
不过这是什么？谁送来的？
But what is it? Who's it from?
气色不错
Looking good.
我决定接受老套的安排
I decided to embrace the cliché.
利用坐牢的时间来好好健身
and use my time in jail to get ripped.
比你之前的目标强多了
You've had worse goals.
我的律师也这样说
So my lawyers tell me.
你呢？回特许局吗？
And you? Back with the Charter?
对 我回特许局了
Yeah, I'm back with the Charter.
不过有两个条件
But on two conditions.
谍心是个很棒的工具
The Heart's an amazing tool.
但仅是工具而已
But that's all it is.
如果我们只看几率行事
If we only follow the odds,
不管几率如何 都成不了大事
we'll never do anything in spite of the odds.
如果几率建议按兵不动 那该怎么办？
And what if the odds tell you to do nothing?
那他们就会派我出马
That's when they send me.
第二件事是什么？
What's the second thing?
我喜欢我的队友 凯娅
I liked my team, Keya.
我想念他们
I miss them.
我希望跟心怀天下的人共事
I wanna surround myself with people who will change the world for good.
（鬼牌）
怎么了 杰克？
How we doing, Jack?
有好消息 也有坏消息
Good news and bad news.
好消息 我勘察了广场
The good news, I've scouted the square,
你的计划可能会奏效
And your plan just might work.
坏消息…
The bad news--
燕麦奶卖完了
Uh, they were out of oat milk.
杰克
-Jack.
怎么？是你让我混入其中的
What? You told me to blend in.
我们攻进电网了吗？
Did we get into the power grid?
是的 超容易的
Yeah. It wasn't that hard,
因为他们的密码就是“密码”
Because their password was "password."
你的咖啡
Your coffee.
谢谢
Thank you.
是冷的
This is cold.
我们仍然可以送你去吃牢饭 你知道的吧？
Um, you know we can still throw you in jail, right?
嘿
Hey.
别下车
Stay in the van.
我们会老实待着 老大
We stay in the van, boss.
谍心已准备就绪
The Heart's all set.
调虎离山计呢？
And the diversion?
准备好了
Ready.
给他们个痛快
Go give them the bam.
向来如此
Always.